
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "Who Invented  PI π ?",
    answer: "William Jones",
    options: [
      "William Jones",
      "Hero of Alexandria",
      "Aryabhata",
      "Isaac Newton"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "If 5x-4 = 26,What does x equal?",
    answer: "6",
    options: [
      "5",
      "6",
      "9",
      "8",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "A simple closed curve made up of only _____________ is called a polygon ?",
    answer: "line segments",
    options: [
      "curves",
      "line segments",
      "lines",
      "closed curves",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "Who is the Father of Mathematics?",
    answer: "Archimedes",
    options: [
      "Srinivasa Ramanujan",
      "Pythagoras",
      "Archimedes",
      "Leonhard Euler"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "Who invented the algebra?",
    answer: "Muhammad ibn Musa al-Khwarizmi",
    options: [
      "Albert Einstein",
      "Muhammad ibn Musa al-Khwarizmi",
      "David Hilbert",
      "Ada Lovelace"
    ]
  },
  

   {
    numb: 6,
    question: "Who invented e=mc2 ?",
    answer: "Albert Einstein",
    options: [
      "Euclid",
      "David Hilbert",
      "Archimedes",
      "Albert Einstein"
    ]
  },

  {
    numb: 7,
    question: "who invented number 0 ?",
    answer: "Brahmagupta",
    options: [
      "Bhāskara II",
      "Brahmagupta",
      "Carl Friedrich Gauss",
      "C. P. Ramanujam"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 8,
    question: " All the angles of a regular polygon are of ________________.?",
    answer: "equal measure",
    options: [
      "90°",
      "60°",
      "equal measure",
      "equal length",
    ]
  }, 
  {
    numb: 9,
    question: "The area of a square of side a is ?",
    answer: "a²",
    options: [
      "a",
     "a²",
    " 2a",
     "4a",
    ]
  },

  {
    numb: 10,
    question: " 1 cm³ = ?",
    answer: " 0.000001 m³",
    options: [
      " 0.000001 m³",
      " 0.01 m³",
      " 0.1 m³",
      " 1000 m³",
    ]
  },
];